imoviewindows.com 2018-05-14

# Our Privacy Policy | iMovieWindows

At iMovieWindows site, your security and privacy important to us. We take the following producers to protect your personal information. 

## Order process 

Credit card information in encrypted with SSL technology during the whole ordering process and is deleted as soon as your order is completed. All other personal information (name, address and product ordered) is held to assist delivery of goods (if applicable), and product registration.

## PERSONAL INFORMATION

iMovieWindows collects basic contact information when fill in a contact form. This information will be used for administrative and identification purposes only and will not be shared with our partners or third parties. Personal information is stored on iMovieWindows server and is only accessed by authorized iMovieWindows personnel.

## COOKIES

iMovieWindows uses a cookie to store your visiting and referrer information. A cookie is a small text file, stored on your computer's hard drive, that can be read by our system when you return to our site.

## GENERAL INFORMATION

iMovieWindows also collects general demographic information about visitors to our site. The information we collect creates a broad picture of our population rather than focusing on any one individual. This information is used to continually refine our products and to identify the most popular areas of our site.

## ENCRYPTED CREDIT CARD PURCHASES

If you use a credit card to purchase a iMovieWindows product, the credit card number is encrypted as it passes over the internet. Your credit card number is not kept or recorded by iMovieWindows or our computers - it is simply passed through to the credit card company to purchase the product you want. In this respect, buying a product from iMovieWindows is similar to a credit card purchase at any store. Neither iMovieWindows nor the store keeps your credit card number on file.

We value our privacy and we value yours, too. It is our goal to make your experience with iMovieWindows a safe and positive experience.
